blogsuccessjournal.com 2016-12-29

# Privacy Policy - BlogPress

Last Updated on 03/30/2016

BlogPress takes your privacy seriously. We will not sell, lease, or exchange your personal data to, or otherwise share your personal data with, third parties in ways other than described in this Privacy Policy.

This Privacy Policy governs all use of the BlogPress website (blogpressdev.com) and all content, services and products available at or through the website, including, but not limited to, the BlogPress hosting and domain name services (“BlogPress”), (taken together, the Website). The Website is owned and operated by Dan & Jennifer Media, Inc. Dan & Jennifer Media, Inc. is the sole owner of information collected on the Website.

The Website is offered subject to your acceptance without modification of all of the terms and conditions contained herein and all other operating rules, policies (including, without limitation, the [BlogPress Terms of Service](http://blogpressdev.com/terms/ "BlogPress Terms of Service")) and procedures that may be published from time to time on the Website by BlogPress (collectively, the “Agreement”).

## Information Collection And Use

### Registration

The BlogPress service requires a login in order to provide you with a personalized account. During our account registration process, we will collect a login name, password, and an email address from you. You must provide all of this information in order to obtain an account. After completing our registration form, you will receive a welcome email describing your new BlogPress account, and how to access that account. You may, at your option, also store your social media and other third-party credentials as part of your account with BlogPress.

### Account Subscriptions

When you create an account, BlogPress will collect personally identifiable information (credit card number, billing address, phone number). This information is stored by our secure PCI compliant payment processing service in order to process your recurring invoices. This information is only used to verify credit card authenticity, and issue invoices as per your service agreement.

If we are unable to process your subscription for a given month, this information, along with your account information, may be used to contact you.

### Hosted Websites

Other BlogPress members hosting websites with BlogPress are given tools that may ask you to optionally enter your email address when making comments on their website, or contacting them through their website. Since other members on BlogPress can manipulate the HTML code on their site directly, there are opportunities available for a malicious user to inject code that would log your information before it reaches our system. In addition, once in our system, website owners will have the opportunity to review and modify any information entered into their website. Since we do not have full control over how members run their individual sites, this privacy policy does not apply to any hosted BlogPress website that you do not own. You should check that you trust the owner of a particular website before submitting personally identifiable information on that site.

### Server Logs

When accessing web pages on the Website domain, BlogPress may log your IP address, access URL, time of access, browser type, and referral URL in order to provide us with internal information regarding site traffic statistics. This information may also be used to identify users who are using the service for spam or other activity that is deemed in conflict with our Terms of Service. This information is used in the aggregate and is never linked back to any personally identifiable information.

## Removal Of Personally Identifiable Information

To remove your personally identifiable information from our system, submit your account and/or website for deletion via our customer support form. Your personal information will be removed within 2 business days, though your actual login name will remain reserved on our system until re-collection.

## Communications from BlogPress

### Website-related Announcements

BlogPress uses information collected through the Website to send out notifications regarding service related issues (such as maintenance periods, billing problems, account expiration, and other items that may impact service). Generally, you may not opt-out of these communications, which are not promotional in nature. If you do not wish to receive them, you have the option to deactivate your account.

### Other Messages

We may also send you messages from time to time about new features or services that we will offer to our users. You may opt-out of these communications at any time by clicking on the link at the bottom of our communications to you, or by changing your preferences in your email profile.

### Customer Website

Upon issuing a customer support request to BlogPress, we may use your information and email address to contact you regarding your inquiry.

## Information Sharing and Disclosure

### Aggregate Information (non-personally identifiable)

We share aggregated demographic information about our user base with our advertisers. This information does not identify individual users. This information contains statistics related to traffic and the geographic location of our customers. We also may share aggregated user information with third parties who help us to analyze our user base to improve the Website.

We do not link aggregate user data with personally identifiable information.

### Personally Identifiable Information

BlogPress employs third-party service providers to perform functions on our behalf. Examples include credit card processing, email service providers, analyzing data, providing customer service. These service providers have access to personal information needed to perform their functions, but may not use it for any other purposes.

In the event of a business transfer or sale by BlogPress, customer information generally is one of the transferred business assets but remains subject to the commitments made in any pre-existing Privacy Policy (unless, of course, you consent otherwise).

We may release account and other personal information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law; enforce or apply our Terms of Website; or protect the rights, property, or safety of BlogPress, our users, or others. This includes exchanging information with other companies and organizations for fraud protection and credit risk reduction.

Other than as set out above, you will receive notice when information about you might go to third parties, and you will have an opportunity to choose not to share the information.

## Log Files

As is true of most websites, we gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, Internet Service Provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp, and clickstream data.

We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users’ movements around the Website and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. We do not link this automatically-collected data to personally identifiable information.

## Cookies

Like most websites, we use small bits of data called cookies stored on users’ computers to simulate a continuous connection. Cookies let us ‘remember’ information about your preferences and passwords and allow you to move within our Website without reintroducing yourself. Members who disable cookies will not be able to use the Website, as they are required to maintain your login to our service within a browser session. Disabling cookies does not prevent you from accessing websites published under our system, though some features of those sites may be degraded.

These cookies can be tied back to personally identifiable information only in the event that you are logged in to our Website. If you are logged in to our Website, the cookies on your computer will uniquely identify your account within our system.

This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by BlogPress only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. See the ‘Third Party Advertisers’ section for more details.

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See Third Party Advertisers.

## Member Websites

Certain information, such as your name and IP address are logged by our system when posting messages to other member websites via comments, forums, or chat rooms, and are made available to the owner of the website you are posting on. These items may be displayed to readers of the site you are posting on, depending on the settings of that particular site. If you would not like to have these details disclosed, refrain from posting messages to any BlogPress member site not owned by you.

## Links to Other Sites

This Website contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by BlogPress Please be aware that we, BlogPress, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites.

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information.

This Privacy Policy applies only to information collected by this Website.

## Business Transitions

In the event BlogPress goes through a business transition, such as a merger, acquisition by another company, or sale of all or a portion of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information.

## Legal Disclaimer

We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Website.

## Changes in this Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this Privacy Policy and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. We will not materially change our policies and practices to make them less protective of customer information collected in the past without the consent of affected customers.

We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this Privacy Policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice within your BlogPress Dashboard.

## Contact Us

If you have any questions or suggestions regarding our privacy policy, please [contact us](http://blogpressdev.com/support/ "Contact Support – We Got This!").
